<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>People on Kowarsky Ritson LLP</title>
    <link>/people/</link>
    <description>Recent content in People on Kowarsky Ritson LLP</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/people/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Anita Chand</title>
      <link>/people/anita-chand/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/anita-chand/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asaf Mallek</title>
      <link>/people/asaf-mallek/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/asaf-mallek/</guid>
      <description>Asaf has a wide-ranging litigation practice and has appeared on behalf of his clients before the BC Court of Appeal, the BC Supreme Court, Bankruptcy Court, the BC Provincial Court, Workers&amp;rsquo; Compensation Appeal Tribunal (WCAT), WorkSafeBC, and the BC Human Rights Tribunal. He has experience in a wide range of legal matters ranging from commercial litigation to family law to administrative and tribunal law.
He received a Master of Laws with Commendation from City, University of London (2011), a Bachelor of Laws with Honours from Cardiff University (2009), and a Bachelor of Arts from University of British Columbia (2000).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eoin Logan</title>
      <link>/people/eoin-logan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/eoin-logan/</guid>
      <description>Eoin joined Kowarsky Ritson LLP in 2015 and has a burgeoning litigation practice. He has represented clients at the Supreme Court of British Columbia and Provincial Courts all over the Lower Mainland. He currently works in various areas of law including of collections, foreclosure, contract litigation, general civil litigation, commercial disputes and family law
Eoin was called to the bar in 2017 having completed his articles with the firm. Eoin completed his law degree and LLM at UCC in Cork, Ireland before completing the NCA exams to be called to the bar in British Columbia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jacob B. Kowarsky</title>
      <link>/people/jacob-kowarsky/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/jacob-kowarsky/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joselina Silva</title>
      <link>/people/joselina-silva/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/joselina-silva/</guid>
      <description>Joselina Silva is Kowarsky Ritson’s Bookkeeper and has had over 20 years of experience in Accounting. In addition, she provides a supportive role in many aspects of organization and management of files, including correspondence with clients and related parties.
Outside of work, her interests include travelling, reading, and spending time with her friends and family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lagrimas Tamayao</title>
      <link>/people/lagrimas-tamayao/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/lagrimas-tamayao/</guid>
      <description>Lagrimas returned to Kowarsky Ritson in 2017 as the Firm’s Receptionist. She is responsible for the day-to-day work of the front desk, and provides a wide range of administrative support, including preparation of Mortgage documents and communication with clients and related parties.
Her interests outside of work include Visiting with friends and relatives, strolling around, having picnic of just hanging out. Likes outdoor activities. Takes care of individuals with disabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ori J. Kowarsky</title>
      <link>/people/ori-kowarsky/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/ori-kowarsky/</guid>
      <description>Ori has a wide-ranging litigation practice and has appeared on behalf of his clients before the BC Court of Appeal, the BC Supreme Court, the Federal Court of Canada, Bankruptcy Court, every level of Provincial Court, Worksafe/BC and the BC Human Rights Tribunal. He has over fourteen years’ experience in a wide range of legal matters ranging from commercial litigation to family law to administrative and tribunal law.
Ori is also an award-winning filmmaker and his continuing work in that field informs his film, television and new media practice for local and international filmmakers and artists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pei Yi Yeh</title>
      <link>/people/pei-yeh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/pei-yeh/</guid>
      <description>Pei has a wide range of experience in legal matters from personal injury to creditors’ remedies and corporate law. She regularly appears in the BC Provincial Court and Supreme Court on behalf of her clients.
Pei was called to the bar in 2018 after articling with Kowarsky Ritson LLP. She received an LLB from the University of Edinburgh, an M.Litt. in Philosophy from St. Andrews University, and a BA in Political Science from McGill University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Richard W.H. Ritson</title>
      <link>/people/richard-ritson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/richard-ritson/</guid>
      <description>Richard has been a trusted advisor to his clients for over 20 years, and a partner in the firm since 2002. He has a varied practice including wills, probate/estate administration, elder law, private business advising, and real estate, mortgage and collections/foreclosure work.
He received a Bachelor of Laws from the University of Victoria (1988) and a Bachelor of Arts (Hons.) in History from the University of Western Ontario (1985).
Richard was called to the Bar in British Columbia in 1989, and has practised law since that time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shirley Fang</title>
      <link>/people/shirley-fang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/shirley-fang/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>